...I heard
Water Imps have a special elixir...
I know...
Could that be the secret
Behind the Prima Donna's voice...?
Wait, shhh...!
If only I could sing like the Prima Donna
I'd do anything. Whatever it takes...
Whatever it takes...?
Prima Donna!?
...I'm sorry, Prima Donna!
I just—
Want to be a singer?
Yes...
Why?
The troupe is the only place
...I won't go hungry
I know it's a selfish reason, but I...
No
I actually find it quite admirable
Here, this will help your voice
But first
Tell me
What do you want your voice to sound like?
Sound like...?
Perhaps...
As soft
Gentle
And sweet as a childhood dream
Or passionate and brilliant
A voice capable of commanding center stage
Or perhaps something colder
That feeling of farewell or a final curtain call
Then...
Which one would you choose? Which kind of voice?
I wouldn't choose any single "one"
My voice drifts between a multitude of possibilities, wandering to and fro...
...Endlessly searching for a path that leads toward home
I'm sorry, Prima Donna
But I... I still don't understand...
Heh
Long to be someone else
And you're bound to forget your own voice
But I like the answer you gave
The way I see it...
You're more in tune with your heart than most
So...
...Take this lozenge
And we can start practicing in a bit
...Huh? Lozen—
Prima Donna!?
—Mmph... —Hahaha
After that, go practice another run of high notes...
Ah, no, make it three
Oh
And no more talk of this "elixir" for now
*sigh* That was the last of my lozenges